Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 1989.0080
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Joseph M. Rourke Files, undated, 1948-1962
  - Subseries A: General Administrative Files, undated, 1948-1954
    - Union Label Leagues, 1951, 1954 (Box 3:, Folder 140)
      - Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 3:, Folder 150)
    - United labor Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 3:, Folder 151-152)
    - United labor Committee Conference, 1951 (Box 3:, Folder 153)
    - Union Holding Company, 1952 (Box 3:, Folder 154)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, 1953 (Box 3:, Folder 155)
    - U.S. Government, Administrative, 1954 (Box 3:, Folder 156)
    - U.S. Senate and House bills, 1952 (Box 3:, Folder 157)
    - Vocational rehabilitation— Consulting Committee, 1954 (Box 3:, Folder 158)
    - Vocational rehabilitation, undated (Box 3:, Folder 159)
    - Velleman, Aaron, 1954 (Box 3:, Folder 160)
    - Wage clarification orders, 1951 (Box 3:, Folder 161)
    - Worker's Educational Service, University of Michigan, 1947-1948 (Box 3:, Folder 162)
    - Woodhouse, Chase Going, 1950-1952 (Box 3:, Folder 163)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 164)
  - Subseries B: General Administrative Files, 1954-1962
    - AFL-CIO, 1955 (Box 4:, Folder 165)
      - Community Services Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 166)
      - Department of Legislation, 1959, 1960 (Box 4:, Folder 167-168)
      - Executive Council, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 169)
      - News Service, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 170)
      - News releases, 1957-1959 (Box 4:, Folder 171)
      - Testimonies, 1959 (Box 4:, Folder 172)
    - Affiliated local unions, 1955-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 173-175)
      - Association of American Street Railway Employees, 1955 (Box 4:, Folder 176)
      - Allied Industrial Workers, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 177)
      - American Federation of Teachers, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 178)
      - Autoworkers, 1957-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 179)
      - Barbers, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 180)
      - Bookbinders, 1961 (Box 4:, Folder 181)
      - Boot and shoe workers, 1961 (Box 4:, Folder 182)
      - Bricklayers, 1956-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 183)
      - Bridgeport Central Labor Union, 1955, 1958 (Box 4:, Folder 184)
      - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 185)
      - Building services employees, 1959-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 186)
      - Building trades, 1954 (Box 4:, Folder 187)
      - Carpenters, 1956-1960 (Box 4:, Folder 188-190)
      - Central Labor Unions
        - Bristol, 1956 (Box 4:, Folder 191)
        - Danbury, 1957-1958 (Box 4:, Folder 192)
        - Hartford, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 193)
        - Middletown, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 194)
        - New Britain, 1956 (Box 4:, Folder 195)
        - New Haven, 1954-1958 (Box 4:, Folder 196)
        - New London, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 197)
      - Chemical workers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 198)
      - Doll and toy workers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 199)
      - Electrical workers (IBEW), 1956-1960 (Box 4:, Folder 200-202)
      - Electricians (IUE), 1957-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 203)
      - Electrotypers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 204)
      - Elevator constructors, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 205)
      - Engineers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 206)
      - Photo engravers, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 207)
      - Federal Labor Union, 1960 (Box 4:, Folder 208)
      - Firefighters, 1954-1962 (Box 4:, Folder 209-210)
      - Furniture workers, 1957-1960 (Box 4:, Folder 211)
      - Garment workers, 1956-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 212)
      - Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 213)
      - Glove Workers Union, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 214)
      - Government Employees, 1955, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 215)
      - Handbag, Luggage, belt and novelty workers, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 216)
      - Hatters, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 217)
      - Hod carriers, 1956-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 218)
      - Hotel and restaurant employees, 1955-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 219)
      - Insurance agents, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 220)
      - Iron workers, 1955-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 221)
      - Jewelry workers, 1956-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 222)
      - Lathers, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 223)
      - Laundry carriers, 1955-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 224)
      - Letter carriers, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 225)
      - Machinists, 1956-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 226-227)
      - Maintenance and way employees, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 228)
      - Meatcutters, 1954-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 229)
      - Molders, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 230)
      - Musicians, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 231)
      - “M”, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 232)
      - Office Employees, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 233)
      - Painters, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 234)
      - Paper makers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 235)
      - Pattern makers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 236)
      - Plumbers, 1955-1959 (Box 4:, Folder 237)
      - Polishers and buffers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 238)
      - Porters, sleeping car, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 239)
      - Post Office clerks, 1956-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 240-241)
      - Post Office mail handlers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 242)
      - Postal employees, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 243)
      - Printing pressmen, 1955-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 244)
      - Postal Transport Association, National, 1955 (Box 4:, Folder 245)
      - Public Employees, Leo Kramer, International Rep., 1955-1956 (Box 4:, Folder 246)
      - Public Employees, 1956-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 247)
      - Pulp and sulphite workers, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 248)
      - Railway carmen, firemen and signalmen, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 249)
      - Railway clerks, 1955-1960 (Box 4:, Folder 250)
      - Railway patrolmen, 1955, 1960 (Box 4:, Folder 251)
      - Retail clerks, 1955-1960 (Box 4:, Folder 252)
      - Rooters, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 253)
      - Rubber workers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 254)
      - Sheet metal workers, 1955-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 255)
      - Special delivery messengers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 256)
      - State, County and Municipal Employees, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 257)
        - Council, 1958-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 258-259)
      - Steamfitters, 1955-1957 (Box 4:, Folder 260)
      - Steelworkers, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 261)
      - Stereotypes, 1956 (Box 4:, Folder 262)
      - Switchmen, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 263)
      - Teachers, 1955-1958 (Box 4:, Folder 264)
      - Teamsters, 1955-1962 (Box 4:, Folder 265-266)
      - Technical engineers, 1961 (Box 4:, Folder 267)
      - Telephone workers, 1955-1961 (Box 4:, Folder 268)
      - Telegraphers, 1957 (Box 5:, Folder 269)
      - Textile workers, 1955-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 270)
      - Theatrical stage employees, 1955-1959 (Box 5:, Folder 271)
      - Typographical, 1955-1962 (Box 5:, Folder 272)
      - United Mine Workers, 1955-1960 (Box 5:, Folder 273)
      - United Steel Workers, 1959-1960 (Box 5:, Folder 274)
      - Wine workers, 1957 (Box 5:, Folder 275)
    - Albrecht, William, 1955-1956 (Box 5:, Folder 276)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1955, 1957 (Box 5:, Folder 277)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1957 (Box 5:, Folder 278)
    - American Federation of Labor, 1955-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 279-281)
    - “B”, 1956-1961 (Box 5:, Folder 282)
    - Barry, Frank, 1954-1956 (Box 5:, Folder 283)
    - Bartlett, John H., 1955 (Box 5:, Folder 284)
    - Biemiller, Andrew J., 1955-1960 (Box 5:, Folder 285-286)
    - Borchardt, Selma M., 1956 (Box 5:, Folder 287)
    - Greater Bridgeport Labor Council By-Laws, 1959 (Box 5:, Folder 288)
    - Building and Construction Trade Department, 1955-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 289)
    - Building Trades Council, 1958-1961 (Box 5:, Folder 290)
    - Central Labor Councils, 1958-1961 (Box 5:, Folder 291)
    - Citizens for a CT Constitutional Convention, 1955 (Box 5:, Folder 292)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1955-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 293)
    - Civil Rights Committee—minutes, 1956 (Box 5:, Folder 294-295)
    - Clerkin, James, 1955 (Box 5:, Folder 296)
    - Connecticut
      - Advisory Council, 1957 (Box 5:, Folder 297)
      - Apprenticeship Council, 1956-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 298)
      - Association of Electrical Workers, 1955-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 299)
      - Bureau of Employment Security, Joseph M. Tone, 1955-1956 (Box 5:, Folder 300)
      - Civil Defense, 1959-1960 (Box 5:, Folder 301)
      - Commission on Forfeited Rights (Box 5:, Folder 302)
      - Commissioner of Labor, Renato Ricciciuti, 1956-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 303)
      - Deputy Commissioner of Labor, Leo J. Dunn, 1956-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 304)
      - Committee on Civil Rights, 1955-1958 (Box 5:, Folder 305)
      - Committee to Combat Discrimination in Housing, 1954-1960 (Box 5:, Folder 306)
      - Committee for Equal Opportunity in Housing, 1954-1960 (Box 5:, Folder 307)
      - Committee for Labor Israel, 1956-1961 (Box 5:, Folder 308)
      - Committee for the Rehabilitation of the Mentally Handicapped, 1956-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 309)
      - Council for Educational Television, 1955 (Box 5:, Folder 310)
      - Council for Retarded Children, Inc., 1955 (Box 5:, Folder 311)
      - Department of Education, 1956-1958 (Box 5:, Folder 312)
      - Departments, Miscellaneous, 1956-1962 (Box 5:, Folder 313)
      - Development Commission, 1955-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 314)
      - Education Association, 1955-1956 (Box 5:, Folder 315-316)
      - Employment Security Division, 1956-1961 (Box 5:, Folder 317)
      - Federation of Labor, 1954-1955 (Box 5:, Folder 318)
      - Federation of Labor—History, 1955-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 319)
      - Federation of Planning and Zoning Agencies, 1960 (Box 5:, Folder 320)
      - Federationists, 1954-1957 (Box 5:, Folder 321)
      - Governor's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, 1957-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 322-323)
      - Health League, 1959-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 324)
      - Higher Education Assistance Corporation, 1959-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 325)
      - Israel Histadrut Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 6:, Folder 326)
      - Mediation and Arbitration Board, 1958-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 327)
      - Mental Health Association, 1955-1960 (Box 6:, Folder 328)
      - Personnel Department, 1959-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 329)
      - Public Expenditure Council, Inc., 1955, 1957 (Box 6:, Folder 330)
      - Secretary of the State, 1957, 1960 (Box 6:, Folder 331)
      - Temporary Commission on Housing, 1957 (Box 6:, Folder 332)
      - Tuberculosis Association, Inc., 1955 (Box 6:, Folder 333)
      - University of, 1954, 1961 (Box 6:, Folder 334-336)
      - Volunteers for Civil Rights, 1955-1956 (Box 6:, Folder 337)
      - Workingmen, History of, 1955 (Box 6:, Folder 338)
    - Committee for National Trade Policy, 1958-1960 (Box 6:, Folder 339)
    - Cruikshank, Nelson H., 1955-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 340)
    - “D”, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 341)
    - Danbury Labor Council, 1961 (Box 6:, Folder 342)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1957-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 343)
    - Democratic National Committee Newsletter, 1960 (Box 6:, Folder 344)
    - Democratic and Republican Platforms, 1956 (Box 6:, Folder 345)
    - Democratic State Central Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 6:, Folder 346)
    - Dix (Fort), 1955-1956 (Box 6:, Folder 347)
    - Donnelly, Joseph F. (Msgr.), 1957 (Box 6:, Folder 348)
    - Education, Department of, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 349)
    - Family Services of New Haven, 1959 (Box 6:, Folder 350)
    - Federation of University Teachers, 1959-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 351)
    - Financial Reports ( AFL-CIO), 1955-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 352)
    - Freedom Crusade, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 353)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 354)
    - “G”, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 355)
    - Galullo, James, 1955-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 356)
    - “H”, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 357)
    - Hartford Labor Council, Greater, 1958-1961 (Box 6:, Folder 358)
    - Henle, Peter, 1955-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 359)
    - Holy Family Retreat House, 1956-1958 (Box 6:, Folder 360)
    - Houle, Arthur, 1955 (Box 6:, Folder 361)
    - “I”, 1957 (Box 6:, Folder 362)
    - Industrial Union Department, 1957 (Box 6:, Folder 363)
    - Irwin, Elizabeth [photographs], undated (Box 6:, Folder 364)
    - Johnson, Oscar, 1957-1958 (Box 6:, Folder 365)
    - Joint Council of Industrial Unions, 1955-1958 (Box 6:, Folder 366)
    - Junior Achievement, Inc., 1955 (Box 6:, Folder 367)
    - “K”, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 368)
    - Kalaski, Victor, 1956 (Box 6:, Folder 369)
    - Knights of Columbus, 1955-1959 (Box 6:, Folder 370-371)
    - Kohler strike, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 372-374)
    - News releases, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 375)
    - “L”, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 376)
    - Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 377)
    - Labor organizations: foreign, international, 1958 (Box 7:, Folder 378)
    - League of Women Voters of CT, 1960-1961 (Box 7:, Folder 379)
    - League of Women Voters pamphlets, newsletters, 1958-1961 (Box 7:, Folder 380)
    - Lee, Richard C. (Mayor), 1958-1961 (Box 7:, Folder 381)
    - Livingston, Max, 1957 (Box 7:, Folder 382)
    - Lubin Office Furniture Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 7:, Folder 383)
    - “M”, 1957 (Box 7:, Folder 384)
    - Machinists, International Association of, 1956 (Box 7:, Folder 385)
    - Manning, Justin F., 1955-1960 (Box 7:, Folder 386)
    - Meany, George, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 387-388)
    - Merge Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 389)
    - Metal Trades Division (AFL), 1955 (Box 7:, Folder 390)
    - McGavin, Peter, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 391)
    - McGuire, Peter J. Memorial, 1955-1956 (Box 7:, Folder 392)
    - Middletown Release Slip System, 1956 (Box 7:, Folder 393)
    - Myers, Robert, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 394)
    - “N”, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 395)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1955-1958 (Box 7:, Folder 396)
    - National Child Labor Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 397)
    - National Committee for Labor Israel pamphlets, 1956-1958 (Box 7:, Folder 398)
    - National Labor Council Conference of Christians and Jews, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 399)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1961 (Box 7:, Folder 400)
    - National Legislative Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 401)
    - New England State Federation of Labor, 1955, 1957 (Box 7:, Folder 402)
    - New Haven
      - Citizens Action Commission, 1955-1958 (Box 7:, Folder 403-407)
      - Clock Company Union, 1958-1959 (Box 7:, Folder 408)
      - Curative Workshop, 1955 (Box 7:, Folder 409)
      - Housing Authority, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 410)
      - Human Relations Council, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 411-412)
      - Intergroup Study Committee, The Greater, 1958 (Box 7:, Folder 413)
      - Other Departments, 1960 (Box 7:, Folder 414)
      - Redevelopment Agency, 1959-1960 (Box 7:, Folder 415)
    - Organizing, 1955 (Box 7:, Folder 416)
    - Organizing pamphlets: correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 7:, Folder 417)
    - Organizing pamphlets, 1951-1956 (Box 7:, Folder 418)
    - Page, Jerry, 1955 (Box 7:, Folder 419)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Physically Handicapped, 1960-1961 (Box 7:, Folder 420)
    - President's Committee—Government contracts, 1959 (Box 7:, Folder 421)
    - “R”, 1957 (Box 7:, Folder 422)
    - Reardon, Harold F., 1955 (Box 7:, Folder 423)
    - Reference letters, 1955-1958 (Box 7:, Folder 424)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 1957 (Box 7:, Folder 425)
    - Retreat, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 426)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham (Governor ), 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 427)
    - Ricciuti, Renato, Commissioner of Labor, 1958-1961 (Box 7:, Folder 428)
    - Rogers, Richard, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 429)
    - “Right to Work” correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 430-434)
    - “S”, 1956-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 435)
    - Scamporino, Vincent J., 1956 (Box 7:, Folder 436)
    - Schnitzler, William F., 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 437)
    - Scholarship contributions, 1952-1956 (Box 7:, Folder 438)
    - Social Insurance Department, 1955-1957 (Box 7:, Folder 439)
    - Standard Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1958-1960 (Box 8:, Folder 440)
    - State Federations of Labor, 1955-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 441-443)
    - State Prison Industries Advisory Committee, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 444)
    - State Re-employment Rights Committee—State of CT, 1958 (Box 8:, Folder 445)
    - State Social Insurance Legislation—Regional Conference, 1955 (Box 8:, Folder 446)
    - Strikes, miscellaneous: press releases, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 447)
    - Structure of AFL-CIO, 1955-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 448)
    - Sunday Herald, 1955-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 449)
    - Sviridoff, Mitchell, undated (Box 8:, Folder 450)
    - Thompson, Hugh, 1956-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 451)
    - Torrington Labor Council, 1958 (Box 8:, Folder 452)
    - Tully, James F., 1955-1956 (Box 8:, Folder 453)
    - “U” (Box 8:, Folder 454)
    - Union Label Council—Hartford, 1956 (Box 8:, Folder 455)
    - Union Label Leagues, 1955 (Box 8:, Folder 456)
    - Union Label News, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 457)
    - Union Label and Service Trades Department—CFL, 1955-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 458)
    - Union Legislative Committees, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 459)
    - United Nations, 1955-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 460)
    - United Nations Tour [photograph], 1955 (Box 8:, Folder 461)
    - Winchester Organizing Campaign, undated (Box 8:, Folder 462)
      - Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 8:, Folder 463)
      - Flyers, Bulletins, 1951-1955 (Box 8:, Folder 464)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1955 (Box 8:, Folder 465)
    - Workmen's Compensation cases, 1956 (Box 8:, Folder 466)
    - “X,Y,Z”, 1956-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 467)
    - Zolot, Norman, 1955 (Box 8:, Folder 468)
  - Subseries C: Legislative Files, 1948-1961
    - Section 1—State
      - Atomic Energy— Hugh Ward, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 469)
      - Bowles, Chester, 1948-1959 (Box 8:, Folder 470-473)
      - Civil Rights, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 474)
      - Correspondence to Select Groups, 1959-1961 (Box 8:, Folder 475)
      - Employee Welfare Funds, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 476)
      - Foreign Trade
        - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 8:, Folder 477)
        - Pamphlets, 1957-1958 (Box 8:, Folder 478)
      - Graduated Income Tax—Special Session
        - General Assembly 10-9, 1955 (Box 8:, Folder 479-480)
      - Governor's Fiscal Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 481)
      - Labor Committee, 1961 (Box 8:, Folder 482)
      - Legislation, 1955 (Box 8:, Folder 483)
      - Legislature, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 484)
      - Legislative Committee, 1961 (Box 8:, Folder 485)
      - Legislative Proposals, 1957 (Box 9:, Folder 486-488)
      - Low-Cost Rental Housing, 1949 (Box 9:, Folder 489)
      - Minimum wages, 1951 (Box 9:, Folder 490)
      - State Employees, 1957 (Box 9:, Folder 491)
      - State Representatives—New Haven, 1960-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 492-494)
      - State Senators and Representatives, 1959-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 495)
      - Unemployment compensation, 1955-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 496)
      - Wage and Hour Law, 1956-1957 (Box 9:, Folder 497)
    - Section 2—Federal
      - Federal Advisory Council on Employment Security, 1950-1958 (Box 9:, Folder 498)
        - Council minutes, 1949-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 499)
      - Kennelly-Morse Minimum Wage bill S.3758, 1960 (Box 9:, Folder 500)
      - U.S. Senators (various), 1959-1960 (Box 9:, Folder 501)
      - Benton, William, 1950-1952 (Box 9:, Folder 502-504)
      - Bush, Prescott, 1956-1957 (Box 9:, Folder 505-507)
      - Purtell, William, 1956-1957 (Box 9:, Folder 508-510)
      - U.S. Representatives, 1960-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 511)
      - Daddario, Emilio Q., 1959-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 512)
      - Dodd, Thomas, 1050-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 513-515)
      - Giaimo, Robert N., 1959-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 516)
      - Kowalski, 1958-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 517-518)
      - Monagan, John S., 1959-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 519)
      - Sibal, Abner W., 1960-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 520)
      - Seely-Brown, H., 1960 (Box 9:, Folder 521)
      - Voting Records, 1957-1958 (Box 9:, Folder 522)
  - Subseries D: Political Campaigns, 1956-1957
    - Bennet for Congress, 1956 (Box 9:, Folder 523)
    - Dodd for Senate, 1956-1957 (Box 9:, Folder 524)
    - Giaimo for Congress, 1956-1957 (Box 9:, Folder 525)
    - Ward for Congress, 1956 (Box 9:, Folder 526)
- Series II: Ruth Warren Greenberg, undated, 1940-1961
  - Subseries A: Teaching Materials, 1940-1953
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 10:, Folder 527)
    - Collective bargaining, ca. 1947-1948 (Box 10:, Folder 528)
    - Communication, 1953 (Box 10:, Folder 529)
    - Community relations, ca. 1947-1948 (Box 10:, Folder 530)
    - Economics, ca. 1949 (Box 10:, Folder 531)
    - Filmstrip outlines, ca. 1940-1950 (Box 10:, Folder 532)
    - Government, ca. 1940-1950 (Box 10:, Folder 533)
    - Grievance procedure, ca. 1940-1950 (Box 10:, Folder 534)
    - Human relations (minority problems), 1950 (Box 10:, Folder 535)
    - Labor history, 1947-1948 (Box 10:, Folder 536)
    - Labor legislation, 1947 (Box 10:, Folder 537)
    - Leadership training, 1947, 1950 (Box 10:, Folder 538)
    - New members, 1940-1948 (Box 10:, Folder 539)
    - Parliamentary procedure, 1948, 1950 (Box 10:, Folder 540)
    - Public speaking, 1948 (Box 10:, Folder 541)
    - Representative training, 1948 (Box 10:, Folder 542)
    - Trade unionism, 1948 (Box 10:, Folder 543)
    - Union administration, 1946-1950 (Box 10:, Folder 544)
    - Union Counseling, 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 545)
  - Subseries B: Course Materials, 1943-1954
    - Columbia University School of Business, 1943 (Box 10:, Folder 546)
    - Columbia University Teachers College, 1949 (Box 10:, Folder 547-551)
    - Georgia Workers Education Service, 1946-1950 (Box 10:, Folder 552-558)
    - Roosevelt College, Chicago, IL, 1953-1954 (Box 10:, Folder 559-566)
    - University of Wisconsin, School for Workers, 1947 (Box 11:, Folder 567-569)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers
      - Union Institute, 1952 (Box 11:, Folder 570)
      - Mount Holyoke Institute on the United Nations, 1950 (Box 11:, Folder 571)
  - Subseries C: Education and Information [CSLC, AFL-CIO], undated, 1946-1961
    - Adult Education Association, 1955-1957 (Box 11:, Folder 572-574)
    - American Federation of Labor, Department of Education, 1954-1957 (Box 11:, Folder 575-577)
    - AFL-CIO Research Department, 1959 (Box 11:, Folder 578)
    - American Labor Education Service, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 579)
    - Bridgeport Labor Council, 1958 (Box 11:, Folder 580)
    - Bristol Central Labor Union, 1955-1956 (Box 11:, Folder 581)
    - Bowles Campaign, Chester (Congress), 1958 (Box 11:, Folder 582)
    - “C”, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 583)
    - Central Labor Unions, 1955, 1961 (Box 11:, Folder 584)
    - Central Labor Unions Political Committee, 1956 (Box 11:, Folder 585)
    - Committee on Aging and Aged, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 586)
    - Committee on Education and Information, 1954-1957 (Box 11:, Folder 587)
    - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1956-1958 (Box 11:, Folder 588)
    - COPE
      - Handbook, 1960 (Box 11:, Folder 589)
      - Notes, 1957-1958 (Box 11:, Folder 590)
      - Pamphlets, 1958 (Box 11:, Folder 591)
      - Report, 1956-1958 (Box 11:, Folder 592)
      - Rourke, 1956 (Box 11:, Folder 593)
      - Women's Activities, 1956-1959 (Box 11:, Folder 594-596)
    - Community Colleges, 1964-1965 (Box 11:, Folder 597)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 598)
    - Connecticut
      - Committee on Political Education, 1956-1959 (Box 11:, Folder 599)
      - AFL-CIO COPE Fund, 1956 (Box 11:, Folder 600)
      - COPE leaflets, 1958 (Box 11:, Folder 601)
      - COPE—New Haven committee, 1956-1961 (Box 11:, Folder 602)
      - Labor's League for Political Education (LLPE), 1953-1956 (Box 11:, Folder 603-605)
        - Candidate and nominees, 1952-1956 (Box 11:, Folder 606)